BRAD W. MORTON

78 East Padonia | Lutherville - Timonium, MD 21093 | 410-804-5695 | bradwmorton@gmail.com

Objective

My current goal is to break into a professional career of content design in video games. I want to learn from, experience, and enjoy the work I do and know that I am making a difference for both myself and my studio. If I am given the chance and the time to use my skills in this context then I am certain I can be an asset to any team that I am a part of.

Education

Towson University, Towson, MD Bachelor of Science in English (Writing Track), 2012

Skills

Languages: C#, Python, HTML

Software: Unity, Jira, Adobe Creative Suite, MS Office

Work Experience

December 2014 - Present: ZeniMax Online Studios, Hunt Valley, MD

Senior Quality Assurance Tester, Content Team

- •Found and reported bugs and issues ensuring a high level of quality in new and existing content
- •Lead teams of my peers through group tasks in an orderly and efficient manner
- •Provided feedback to developers with a focus on creating a more fun and engaging experience

May 2010 - December 2014: Outback Steakhouse, Baltimore, MD

Maintenance Liaison

- •Performed various back of house tasks to keep the restaurant efficient
- •Provided aid and assistance to servers, bartenders, cooks, and management when necessary

September 2004 - October 2010: Oakcrest Village, Baltimore, MD

Dining Service Captain

- •Oversaw section staff numbering from 5-10 student workers a night
- •Worked alongside management to improve restaurant and service quality

Other Experience / Accomplishments

November 9-11, 2012: Anime USA, Washington, D.C.

Public Safety Personnel

•Oversaw 5,000 (est) attendees alongside a staff of fellow public safety officers •Prevented theft, fights, and disorderly conduct in and around the convention grounds